{
    "CASE_LIST_FILTER": {
        "all_cases_filter":"(patient_type = 'confirmed' or next_form = 'pui_form' or next_form = 'change_pui_status') and transfer_status != 'sent' and transfer_status != 'pending' and stub !='yes' and (current_status != 'closed')",
        "all_contacts_filter":"transfer_status != 'sent' and transfer_status != 'pending'"
    },
    "SEARCH_NAMES": [
        "Aki", "Graham", "Samic", "Jet", "Petty", "Knack", "Elle", "Leer", "Mike", "John",
        "Rick", "Manny", "Bud", "Reggie", "Trate", "Deb", "Holly", "Utant", "Yu", "Penny",
        "Mick", "Paul", "Clark", "Rib", "Tube", "Sir", "Kim", "Ville", "Louis", "Mello",
        "Marsha", "Moe", "Thegrass", "Smith", "Cooke", "Edoh", "Gail", "Sharon", "Faye", "Anna",
        "Jim", "Mal", "Aaron", "Practice", "Mull", "Zack", "Lou", "Zing", "Tara", "Zona",
        "Carrie", "Abel", "Body", "Jimmy", "Frank", "Manuel", "Labor", "Phil", "Erup", "Doug",
        "Mel", "Chip", "Paige", "Turner", "Sue", "Dante", "Gene", "Jacket", "Sven", "Ed",
        "Matt", "Bill", "Emia", "Zupp", "Greta", "Life", "Barney", "Cull", "Eda", "Barry",
        "Monty", "Minnie", "Mack", "Strone", "Owen", "Lewis", "Kat", "Sal", "Joyce", "Tick",
        "Ty", "Ira", "Shee", "Marcus", "Sil", "Antro", "Mark", "Ette", "Poppa", "Tom"
    ],
    "FUNC_MAIN_SCREEN": {
        "title":"NY App - locust test"
    },
    "FUNC_USER_CHECK_IN_FORM": {
        "title":"Check In"
    },
    "FUNC_USER_CHECK_IN_FORM_SUBMIT": {
        "submitResponseMessage":"Form successfully saved!"
    },
    "FUNC_ALL_CASES_CASE_LIST": {
        "title":"All Cases"
    },
    "FUNC_ALL_OPEN_CASES_CASE_LIST": {
        "title":"All Open Cases"
    },
    "FUNC_ALL_CLOSED_CASES_CASE_LIST": {
        "title":"All Closed Cases"
    },
    "FUNC_MY_CASES_CASE_LIST": {
        "title":"My Cases"
    },
    "FUNC_VIEW_CASE_ASSIGNMENTS_CASE_LIST": {
        "title":"View Case Assignments"
    },
    "FUNC_ALL_CONTACTS_CASE_LIST": {
        "title":"All Contacts"
    },
    "FUNC_ALL_OPEN_CONTACTS_CASE_LIST": {
        "title":"All Open Contacts"
    },
    "FUNC_ALL_CLOSED_CONTACTS_CASE_LIST": {
        "title":"All Closed Contacts"
    },
    "FUNC_MY_CONTACTS_CASE_LIST": {
        "title":"My Contacts: Require Follow-up"
    },
    "FUNC_VIEW_CONTACT_ASSIGNMENTS_CASE_LIST": {
        "title":"View Contact Assignments"
    },
    "FUNC_NEW_SEARCH_ALL_CASES_FORM": {
        "title":"Search Cases", "title2":"Record Search"
    },
    "FUNC_NEW_SEARCH_ALL_CASES": {
        "title":"Search Cases", "title2":"Record Search"
    },
    "FUNC_NEW_SEARCH_ALL_CONTACTS_FORM": {
        "title":"Search Contacts", "title2":"Record Search" 
    },
    "FUNC_NEW_SEARCH_ALL_CONTACTS": {
        "title":"Search Contacts", "title2":"Record Search" 
    },
    "FUNC_ALL_CASES_CASE_DETAILS": {
        "checkKey":"details"
    },
    "FUNC_ALL_CASES_CASE_DETAILS_SUBMIT": {
        "title":"All Cases"
    },
    "FUNC_CI_FORM": {
        "title":"Case Investigation"
    },
    "FUNC_CI_FORM_QUESTIONS": {
        "questions":[
            {"question":"State", "answer":"", "optional":"false", "title":"Case Investigation"},
            {"question":"Race:", "answer":"5", "optional":"false", "title":"Case Investigation"},
            {"question":"Street Address", "answer":"", "optional":"false", "title":"Case Investigation"},
            {"question":"City", "answer":"", "optional":"false", "title":"Case Investigation"},
            {"question":"Gender", "answer":"", "optional":"false", "title":"Case Investigation"},
            {"question":"Preferred Language", "answer":"", "optional":"false", "title":"Case Investigation"},
            {"question":"What date did you get tested?", "answer":"", "optional":"false", "title":"Case Investigation"},
            {"question":"Occupation", "answer":"", "optional":"false", "title":"Case Investigation"}
        ]
    },
    "FUNC_CI_FORM_SUBMIT": {
        "submitResponseMessage":"Form successfully saved!"
    },
    "FUNC_ASSIGN_CASE_FORM": {
        "title":"Assign or Reassign the Case"
    },
    "FUNC_ASSIGN_CASE_FORM_QUESTIONS": {
        "questions":[
            {"question":"Permanently assign the case to a different staff member", "answer":"3", "optional":"false", "title":"Assign or Reassign the Case"},
            {"question":"Permanently reassign case to this staff member", "answer":"", "optional":"false", "title":"Assign or Reassign the Case"}
        ]
    },
    "FUNC_ASSIGN_CASE_FORM_SUBMIT": {
        "submitResponseMessage":"Form successfully saved!"
    },
    "FUNC_CLOSE_PATIENT_RECORD_FORM": {
        "title":"Close the Patient Record"
    },
    "FUNC_CLOSE_PATIENT_RECORD_FORM_QUESTIONS": {
        "questions":[
            {"question":"Are you sure you want to close this record?", "answer":"", "optional":"true", "title":"Close the Patient Record"},
            {"question":"Confirm the patient's outcome or final disposition", "answer":"1", "optional":"true", "title":"Close the Patient Record"},
            {"question":"Are you sure you want to reopen it?", "answer":"", "optional":"true", "title":"Close the Patient Record"}
        ]
    },
    "FUNC_CLOSE_PATIENT_RECORD_FORM_SUBMIT": {
        "submitResponseMessage":"Form successfully saved!"
    },
    "FUNC_ALL_CONTACTS_CASE_DETAILS": {
        "checkKey":"details"
    },
    "FUNC_ALL_CONTACTS_CASE_DETAILS_SUBMIT": {
        "title":"All Contacts"
    },
    "FUNC_CM_FORM": {
        "title":"Contact Monitoring"
    },
    "FUNC_CM_FORM_QUESTIONS": {
        "questions":[
            {"question":"View/Update the rest of the Contact's information", "answer":"1", "optional":"true", "title":"Contact Monitoring"},
            {"question":"Interviewer Name", "answer":"", "optional":"false", "title":"Contact Monitoring"},
            {"question":"Race:", "answer":"2", "optional":"false", "title":"Contact Monitoring"},
            {"question":"Occupation", "answer":"", "optional":"false", "title":"Contact Monitoring"}
        ]
    },
    "FUNC_CM_FORM_SUBMIT": {
        "submitResponseMessage":"Form successfully saved!"
    },




    "FUNC_SEARCH_FOR_DUPLICATE_PATIENT_FORM": {
        "title":"Search for Duplicate Patients",
        "title2":"Record Search"
    },
    "FUNC_SEARCH_FOR_DUPLICATE_PATIENT_SUBMIT": {
        "title":"Search All Cases"
    },
    "FUNC_SEARCH_FOR_DUPLICATE_PATIENT_CASE_DETAILS": {
        "checkKey":"details"
    },
    "FUNC_SEARCH_FOR_DUPLICATE_PATIENT_CASE_DETAILS_SUBMIT": {
        "title":"Search for Duplicate Patients"
    },
    "FUNC_IDENTIFY_DUPLICATE_PATIENT_FORM": {
        "title":"Identify Duplicate Patient"
    },
    "FUNC_IDENTIFY_DUPLICATE_PATIENT_FORM_QUESTIONS": {
        "questions":[
            {"question":"The selected patient is a duplicate of the current patient", "answer":"", "optional":"false", "title":"Identify Duplicate Patient"}
        ]
    },
    "FUNC_IDENTIFY_DUPLICATE_PATIENT_FORM_SUBMIT": {
        "submitResponseMessage":"Form successfully saved!"
    },





    "FUNC_ASSIGN_CONTACT_FORM": {
        "title":"Assign or Re-Assign Contact"
    },
    "FUNC_ASSIGN_CONTACT_FORM_QUESTIONS": {
        "questions":[
            {"question":"Permanently assign the contact to a different staff member", "answer":"3", "optional":"false", "title":"Assign or Re-Assign Contact"},
            {"question":"Permanently reassign contact to this staff member", "answer":"", "optional":"false", "title":"Assign or Re-Assign Contact"}
        ]
    },
    "FUNC_ASSIGN_CONTACT_FORM_SUBMIT": {
        "submitResponseMessage":"Form successfully saved!"
    },
    "FUNC_CLOSE_CONTACT_RECORD_FORM": {
        "title":"Close the Contact Record"
    },
    "FUNC_CLOSE_CONTACT_RECORD_FORM_QUESTIONS": {
        "questions":[
            {"question":"Are you sure you want to close this record?", "answer":"", "optional":"true", "title":"Close the Contact Record"},
            {"question":"Confirm the Contact's outcome or final disposition", "answer":"1", "optional":"true", "title":"Close the Contact Record"},
            {"question":"Are you sure you want to reopen it?", "answer":"", "optional":"true", "title":"Close the Contact Record"}
        ]
    },
    "FUNC_CLOSE_CONTACT_RECORD_FORM_SUBMIT": {
        "submitResponseMessage":"Form successfully saved!"
    },
    "FUNC_RNC_FORM": {
        "title":"Register New Contact(s)"
    },
    "FUNC_RNC_FORM_QUESTIONS": {
        "questions":[
            {"question":"Total number of people in the household (including patient)", "answer":"1", "optional":"false", "title":"Register New Contact(s)"},
            {"question":"First name", "answer":"Locust Test First", "optional":"false", "title":"Register New Contact(s)"},
            {"question":"Last name", "answer":"Locust Test Last", "optional":"false", "title":"Register New Contact(s)"},
            {"question":"Gender", "answer":"2", "optional":"false", "title":"Register New Contact(s)"},
            {"question":"Relationship to case:", "answer":"", "optional":"false", "title":"Register New Contact(s)"},
            {"question":"Occupation", "answer":"", "optional":"false", "title":"Register New Contact(s)"}
        ]
    },
    "FUNC_RNC_FORM_SUBMIT": {
        "submitResponseMessage":"Form successfully saved!"
    },
    "FUNC_BU_CONTACTS_FORM": {
        "title":"Bulk Update Contacts"
    },  
    "FUNC_BU_CONTACTS_FORM_QUESTIONS": {
        "questions":[
            {"question":"Which type of bulk action would you like to take?", "answer":"", "optional":"false", "title":"Bulk Update Contacts"},
            {"question":"Select only open contacts", "answer":"None", "optional":"false", "title":"Bulk Update Contacts"},
            {"question":"Select only contacts with a phone number.", "answer":"None", "optional":"false", "title":"Bulk Update Contacts"},
            {"question":"Select only contacts without a primary owner", "answer":"None", "optional":"false", "title":"Bulk Update Contacts"},
            {"question":"Select only cases without a temporary owner", "answer":"None", "optional":"false", "title":"Bulk Update Contacts"},
            {"question":"Search for contacts matching this criteria", "answer":"", "optional":"false", "title":"Bulk Update Contacts"},
            {"question":"Assign to New Primary Owner", "answer":"", "optional":"false", "title":"Bulk Update Contacts"},
            {"question":"Select the new Primary Owner", "answer":"1", "optional":"false", "title":"Bulk Update Contacts"}
        ]
    },
    "FUNC_BU_CONTACTS_FORM_SUBMIT": {
        "submitResponseMessage":"Form successfully saved!"
    },
    "FUNC_UPDATE_CONTACTS_FORM_SUBMIT": {
        "submitResponseMessage":"Form successfully saved!"
    },
    "FUNC_BU_CASES_FORM": {
        "title":"Bulk Update Cases"
    },
    "FUNC_BU_CASES_FORM_QUESTIONS": {
        "questions":[
            {"question":"Which type of bulk action would you like to take?", "answer":"", "optional":"false", "title":"Bulk Update Cases"},
            {"question":"Select only open cases", "answer":"None", "optional":"false", "title":"Bulk Update Cases"},
            {"question":"Select only cases with a valid phone number.", "answer":"None", "optional":"false", "title":"Bulk Update Cases"},
            {"question":"Search for cases matching this criteria", "answer":"", "optional":"false", "title":"Bulk Update Cases"},
            {"question":"Assign to New Primary Owner", "answer":"", "optional":"false", "title":"Bulk Update Cases"},
            {"question":"Select the new Primary Owner(s)", "answer":"3", "optional":"false", "title":"Bulk Update Cases"}
        ]
    },
    "FUNC_BU_CASES_FORM_SUBMIT": {
        "submitResponseMessage":"Form successfully saved!"
    },
    "FUNC_UPDATE_CASES_FORM_SUBMIT": {
        "submitResponseMessage":"Form successfully saved!"
    },
    "FUNC_MY_TEAM_FORM": {
        "title":"My Team"
    },
    "FUNC_MY_TEAM_FORM_QUESTIONS": {
        "questions":[
            {"question":"Select the Team Member whose contact info you'd like to see:", "answer":"1", "optional":"false", "title":"My Team"}
        ]
    },
    "FUNC_MY_TEAM_FORM_SUBMIT": {
        "submitResponseMessage":"Form successfully saved!"
    },
    "FUNC_RNC_NO_INDEX_FORM": {
        "title":"Register New Contact(s) without Index Case"
    },
    "FUNC_RNC_NO_INDEX_FORM_QUESTIONS": {
        "questions":[
            {"question":"How many new contacts do you want to record?", "answer":"1", "optional":"false", "title":"Register New Contact(s) without Index Case"},
            {"question":"First name", "answer":"Locust Register No Index Test First", "optional":"false", "title":"Register New Contact(s) without Index Case"},
            {"question":"Last name", "answer":"Locust Register No Index Test Last", "optional":"false", "title":"Register New Contact(s) without Index Case"},
            {"question":"Gender", "answer":"2", "optional":"false", "title":"Register New Contact(s) without Index Case"},
            {"question":"Relationship to case:", "answer":"3", "optional":"false", "title":"Register New Contact(s) without Index Case"},
            {"question":"Occupation", "answer":"", "optional":"false", "title":"Register New Contact(s) without Index Case"}
        ]
    },
    "FUNC_RNC_NO_INDEX_FORM_SUBMIT": {
        "submitResponseMessage":"Form successfully saved!"
    },
    "FUNC_RNCASE_FORM": {
        "title":"Register a New Case"
    },
    "FUNC_RNCASE_FORM_QUESTIONS": {
        "questions":[
            {"question":"Complete Full Registration", "answer":"", "optional":"false", "title":"Register a New Case"},
            {"question":"Patient First Name", "answer":"Locust Register New Case First", "optional":"false", "title":"Register a New Case"},
            {"question":"Patient Last Name", "answer":"Locust Register New Case Last", "optional":"false", "title":"Register a New Case"}
        ]
    },
    "FUNC_RNCASE_FORM_SUBMIT": {
        "submitResponseMessage":"Form successfully saved!"
    }
}
